chaseveritt.co.za 2016-05-15

# Chas Everitt Privacy Policy | chaseveritt

The Chas Everitt International Property Group and their independently owned and operated licensed and franchised operations are committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. This privacy policy is for this website ([www.chaseveritt.co.za](http://www.chaseveritt.co.za/)), serviced by the Chas Everitt International Property Group, and governs the privacy of its users who elect to use it.

Our Privacy Policy outlines how we use the information we collect about you as well as how you can let us know if you would prefer to limit the use of that information and procedures that we have in place to safeguard your privacy.

The Chas Everitt International Property Group respects your privacy and as a group we are committed to keeping your information confidential.  
This website and the Chas Everitt International Property Group takes a proactive approach to user privacy and ensure the necessary steps are taken to protect the privacy of its users throughout their visiting experience. This website complies with current South African laws and requirements for user privacy.

In the main, you can visit our website without ever having to divulge any personal information about yourself. It is important to note however that while using this website you may provide information about yourself or it may be collected by us. Any and all information collected on this website will be kept confidential. It will not be sold, loaned, reused or otherwise disclosed to any organisation. This applies to e-mail addresses and all other personal information as well. We gather this information to allow us to process your request and provide you with the information requested by you. 

Chas Everitt will only disclose or report personal information if and when required to do so by law or any regulatory authority and to our staff who require such information to reasonably carry out their duties.

Personal information is used as may be appropriate in the normal course of business to provide the products and services you have requested. Chas Everitt may retain any information for purposes of ongoing business relationships or to communicate directly with you. If any of the information that you have provided to the Chas Everitt International Property Group changes, for example if you change your e-mail address, name or if you wish to cancel your registration, please let us know the correct details by sending an e-mail to [enquiries@everitt.co.za](mailto:enquiries@everitt.co.za).

On written request we will furnish you with details of the personal information we hold about you. You may submit your request via [enquiries@everitt.co.za](mailto:enquiries@everitt.co.za). Should you believe that any information we hold about you is incorrect, please inform us at the above page and we will correct it.

Please note that, while all attempts are made to secure information transmitted to this website, if you are submitting personal details or other information over the Internet which you wish to remain private, there is a possibility that information you submit could be observed by a third party whilst in the process of communication.

  **EMAIL NEWSLETTER**  
This website operates an email newsletter programme, used to inform subscribers about the real estate business and property related general information.

Users can subscribe through an [online automated process](http://www.chaseveritt.co.za/newsletter) should they wish to do so but do so at their own discretion. Some subscriptions may be manually processed through prior written agreement with the user.

Subscriptions are taken in compliance with the legal requirements in South Africa. All personal details relating to subscriptions are held securely. No personal details are passed on to third parties nor shared with companies or people outside of the company that operate this website.

You may request a copy of personal information held about you by this website's email newsletter programme. If you would like a copy of the information held on you please write to [enquiries@everittco.za](mailto:enquiries@everittco.za).

Email marketing campaigns published by this website or its owners may contain tracking facilities within the actual email. Subscriber activity is tracked and stored in a database for future analysis and evaluation. Such tracked activity may include; the opening of emails, forwarding of emails, the clicking of links within the email content, times, dates and frequency of activity and other activities. This information is used to refine future email campaigns and supply the user with more relevant content based around their activity.

In compliance with South African law, subscribers are given the opportunity to unsubscribe at any time through an automated system. This process is detailed at the footer of each email campaign. If an automated un-subscription system is unavailable clear instructions on how to unsubscribe will by detailed instead.

**SOCIAL MEDIA PLATFORMS**  
Communication, engagement and actions taken through external social media platforms that this website and its owners participate on are custom to the terms and conditions as well as the privacy policies held with each social media platform respectively.

Users are advised to use social media platforms wisely and communicate or engage upon them with due care and caution in regard to their own privacy and personal details.

Neither this website nor its owners will ever ask for personal or sensitive information through social media platforms and encourage users wishing to discuss sensitive details to contact them through primary communication channels such as by telephone or email. 

This website uses social sharing buttons which help share web content directly from web pages to the social media platform in question. Users are advised before using such social sharing buttons that they do so at their own discretion and note that the social media platform may track and save your request to share a web page respectively through your social media platform account.

**THIRD PARTY WEBSITE LINKS** This website contains links to third party websites over which the Chas Everitt International Property Group has no control and assumes no responsibility for the content of third party websites or for any losses which may arise out of use of a third party website. The presence of a link to a third party does not necessarily mean that The Chas Everitt International Property Group endorses that site or has any association with the proprietor of that website. 

  Notwithstanding the fact that this website may refer to or provide links to third party websites, your use of such third party websites is entirely at your own risk and we are not responsible for any loss, expense, claim or damage, whether direct, indirect or consequential, arising from your use of such third party websites or your reliance on any information contained thereon. 

**USE OF COOKIES**  
This website uses cookies to better the users experience while visiting the website. Where applicable this website uses a cookie control system allowing the user on their first visit to the website to allow or disallow the use of cookies on their computer, tablet or mobile/device. This complies with legislation requirements for websites to obtain explicit consent from users before leaving behind or reading files such as cookies on a user’s computer, tablet or mobile/device.

Cookies are small files saved to the user's computer hard drive that track, save and store information about the user's interactions and usage of the website. This allows the website, through its server to provide the users with a tailored experience within this website.

Users are advised that if they wish to deny the use and saving of cookies from this website on to their computers hard drive they should take necessary steps within their web browsers security settings to block all cookies from this website and its external serving vendors.

This website uses tracking software to monitor its visitors to better understand how they use it. This software is provided by Google Analytics which uses cookies to track visitor usage. The software will save a cookie to your computer’s hard drive in order to track and monitor your engagement and usage of the website, but will not store, save or collect personal information. You can read Google's privacy policy here for further information [click here.](http://www.google.com/privacy.html)

  **SHORTENED LINKS IN SOCIAL MEDIA**  
This website, the Chas Everitt International Property Group (and its independently owned and operated licensed and franchised operations) through their social media platform accounts may share web links to relevant web pages.

By default some social media platforms shorten lengthy urls. Users are advised to take caution and good judgement before clicking any shortened urls published on social media platforms by this website and its owners. Despite the best efforts to ensure only genuine urls are published many social media platforms are prone to spam and hacking and therefore this website and its owners cannot be held liable for any damages or implications caused by visiting any shortened links.

  **SALE OF BUSINESS    
**In the event that this business is sold, merged, acquired or integrated with another business your details may be disclosed to our advisors and any prospective purchaser/s and their advisors and will be passed on to the new owners of the business.

**GOVERNING LAW**  
These terms and conditions shall be governed and interpreted in accordance with the laws of the Republic of South Africa. Your continued use of the website will constitute your consent and submission to the jurisdiction of the South African courts regarding all proceedings, transactions, applications or the like instituted by either party against the other, arising from any of these terms and conditions.

**Each Chas Everitt Office is independently owned and operated.**

**RESOURCES & FURTHER INFORMATION**
